Ladies and gentlemen welcome
女士们先生们 你们好
My name is Walker Stipe with palo alto education
我是来自Palo Alto Education的Walker Stipe
and today o today to date today
今天，没错就是今天
We have a special treat
我们有特别惊喜
Perhaps you have read or watched
你以前可能读过 或者看过
any portion of the harry potter series
哈利波特系列的其中任意一部分
if you haven't my soul cries out for that sadness
如果你没看过 那真是太可惜了
it is so good it get on it
特别好看而且一直都很棒
this world is a magical world
书中的世界是个魔法世界
this school we see here is Hogwarts
图片上这个学校是霍格沃茨魔法学校
oh my gosh Hogwarts is gorgeous
天啊噜 这个学校棒呆了
Now Hogwarts  is a school as we mentioned
我们提到了霍格沃茨是个学校
if you were to go to the school
如果你在这儿上学
you would be in one of the four classes that this school has
你肯定在四个学校其中一个就学
for instance you could be in Gryffindor
比如说你在格兰芬多
very proud and brave type of person
因为你自豪而勇敢
you could be a Hufflepuff
你可能在赫奇帕奇
very courageous and enduring
因为你勇猛有耐心
you could be a ravenclaw
你可能在拉文克劳
potentially a little bit quirky and brilliant
可能你古怪又聪明
last but not least is the silver and ambition is your aim
最后 你可能在斯莱特林 因为你野心勃勃
and nothing will get in your way
没什么能阻挡你
now to determine which of these houses you will be put into
如果要决定你要去哪个学院
there is no teacher
可没有哪个老师
or professor and no magician shall
教授或者魔法师
take upon themselves this task no no
能完成这项艰难的任务
have a hat you betcha
我们有分院帽 你猜对了
that's what we are making today we're making a hat
我们今天就是要做一顶帽子
welcome to walker stipes haberdashery
欢迎来到walker stipe的杂货铺
where we're gonna make a hat
我们要在这做个帽子
now this hat is a magical hat
这是一顶魔法帽子
whoa magic hats don't mind if I do
哇 魔法帽子诶
and this hat can can tell who you are
这帽子能告诉你你是谁
and tell a lot about you and
你的各种信息
can determine okay this this person has
这个人有很多
of the attributes that I associate with
帽子熟悉的格兰芬多特质
a Gryffindor this guy he's a Gryffindor
所以这个人该去格兰芬多
same house as Harry Potter Hermione and Ronald Weasley themselves
和哈利 赫敏 罗恩一个学院
or perhaps like wow this guy he's a shoot for star
或者这是一个追求卓越的人
like puffett and slyterin and he's one of those guys
比如普菲特和斯莱特林 他是他们中的一员
so we don't have magic
但是我们没有魔法
oh wait yes yes we do yes yes yes yes
等等 我们有啊
yes we do we have machine learning Wow
我们有机器学习呀
machine learning ladies and gentlemen is going bethe magic we use to create our hat
他将会施展魔法为我们造一顶帽子
this hat will enable us to not of course read the minds up
他当然不会教我们读心术
we will bypass that part by merely asking questions
帽子只会问一些问题
and then with those answers that will be what we know about the
有了这些答案 我们就知道
new student at Hogwarts which today is you
霍格沃茨新生 也就是你的信息啦
so welcome to Hogwarts
欢迎来到霍格沃茨
we're gonna make your own magical hat
我们要自己做分院帽咯
let's hop in
让我们开始吧
already we're jumping in first thing you
我们进网站了 首先
want to do you is want to go to machinelearningforkids. com
登陆machinelearningforkids.com
the particular URL you're looking for is this one
你要输入的网址就是这个
but a quick google search of machinelearningforkids should do the trick
google直接搜索也行
so once you are here you want to go to worksheets
进来之后 点击工作表(worksheet)
you go to worksheets and you should hopefully see things look kind of like this
然后你可能会看到这些
what we're doing today is we're doing the sorting hat
我么今天要做的是分院帽
so click on this little guy here
点击这个蓝色按钮
and snag yourself this one this is the dude you want
选择第二个按钮 这是你要做的
what he looks like is this
他看起来怎么样
he looks like this well what a beautiful guy
就是这样 真是漂亮的家伙
this is what we're gonna be working through
我们今天就要在这里做帽子
we've done the conceptual side of getting ourselves ready
我们做好一些概念性的准备工作之后
now what we want to do is we want to get started
然后我们就正式开始啦
so want to go to your projects
进入项目（projects)
make sure you're logged in
确保你已经登陆
this is important otherwise you're you can't save anything
这很重要 不然你什么都保存不了了
so make sure logged in
所以再次确保你已登陆
once you go to projects
点进项目之后
to make a new project
选择创造一个新项目（add a new project）
name it sorting hat or something like that you'll remember
把它命名为分院帽或者你类似的你记得的名字
then what we're doing is we want to Train it
然后我们就要训练它啦 点击训练（train）
by training we need to have some sort of data to train on of course
当然啦 训练的话我们得需要数据
so what data are we training on
所以我们需要怎样的数据呢
well first we need to get our classes
首先我们得有学院的数据
we have our Gryffindor Hufflepuff Slytherin and our ravenclaw houses
我们有格兰芬多 赫奇帕奇 斯莱特林和拉文克劳学院
we need to fill each of these houses
所以我们要给这些学院
with things that are well suited to these to these houses
加上一些符合该学院的信息
so what I did is I went on to the googles
所以我在谷歌上搜索了
and I looked up quotes from particular people who are part of these houses
不同学院不同人说的一些话
for instance for Gryffindor
比如说格兰芬多里
I chose Ronald Weasley because he is one of my favorite
我选择了罗恩 因为他是我最喜欢的角色
for Hufflepuff i chose Ceedric Diggory found some wonderful quotes by him
赫奇帕奇里我选了塞德里克 找到了一些很棒的话
Slytherin of course Draco Malfoy was my go-to character
斯莱特林中 德拉科·马尔福是我寻求协助的角色
then for Ravenclaw Luna Lovegood who is so good so good
拉文克劳里卢娜·洛夫古德非常优秀
she's awesome
她简直太赞了
alright so then we have we have those
然后我们就有这些资料啦
and you do need a lot of them
你们确实需要搜集很多
Afraid to say I did not try with just five of each
遗憾地说我每个学院只试了5个人
but I presume that you do need ten
但我预测你们需要10位
all right once we have done so then then
好吧 一旦我们做好了
then then we go back to project you may
我们就可以回到项目本身
be wondering Walker why did you move over to the side.
你可能会很好奇我为什么会移动鼠标到网页边缘。
Well we're about to find out as we move to the next stage
好吧 我们会发现当我们进行到下一个步骤时
the next stage is where we create the magic
下一个步骤 我们会创造魔法
the magic is about to happen
这个魔法即将发生
ladies and gentlemen get excited what
女士们先生们激动人心的时刻要到了
we're gonna do is entering into the Hall of
我们将要做的就是进入
elements by pressing you learn and test button
元素大厅 通过点击‘learn&test’的按钮
woo the whole elements Woo magical then we shall do the sorcery
噢 这全部的元素简直太神奇了 然后我们将会施展魔法
the sorcery is enacted by waving
这个魔法的创作是通过快速挥舞
our wand very precipitously and then
我们的魔杖 然后
clicking on this button here yes when we
点击这个按钮 当我们
do this it'll take some time  the magic
点击后 需要等待一会儿 魔法生效
takes time but once it is complete then
需要花费一些时间 但是一旦完成
we have a magical hat
我们就会得到一顶魔法帽
the reason I'm over to the side is so
我将鼠标移到这边是为了
that I don't block the button that is
我不会挡住这个按钮 这个按钮的后方
the magic behind that
是魔法的藏身之处
so let us enact the magic
所以让我们施展魔法吧
alrighty this hopefully is what we see on our screen now
好啦 但愿我们在屏幕上看到的正如现在这样
or something very similar to it
或者与这样的画面类似
because this tells us that
因为这告诉了各位
the magic that we have conjured up has done
我们所使用的魔法已经生效了
something something's happened now let's
一些事儿发生了 现在让我们一起
say we're trying to turn a cat into a
说我们正在使一只猫变成一只
dog, a cat into a cup a lamp a house
狗，一只猫变成一个杯子一盏台灯一座房子
whatever maybe a dragon okay we're just
任何东西 或许是一只龙 我们只是
trying to turn it into something
尝试着把它转变成一些东西
in this instance we're trying to turn our
在这个例子里我们正在讲我们的
computer into a hat of course that's
电脑变成一顶帽子 当然那是
that's what we're trying to do.
那是我们正要做的事儿
Now this doesn't mean that it actually turned it
这并不意味着它真的变成了
into a hat that works so let's let's
一只有魔力的帽子 所以让我们
test it let's see if this this guy works
一起测试下 看看这家伙是否真的能运作
I hope I hope that analogy made some sense
我希望 我希望这个比喻能说得通
we're gonna check if this works
我们检查下这个帽子是否行得通
that's what we're doing now alright so
这正是我们在做的 好吧
we're gonna go back we're gonna go into
我们回到之前的步骤 点击
scratch we're gonna open it in scratch
scratch这个按钮 我们点scratch进入这个页面
we're gonna open it in scratch. There is the
我们要打开这个scratch里的页面 这就是
scratch and here is the portion where
scratch的页面 这一部分
you get to have a little bit of fun
你会获得一些乐趣
a little bit of more fun.
更多的一些乐趣
It's for our having a great time to make some artwork yeah
为我们的美好时光做一些插图
get to make some fancy pantsy hats so
做几顶花哨的帽子
you can stick with the wizard hat
所以你可以做巫师帽
if you'd like you don't have to give it
如果你喜欢你不一定要给它
a face you can you can also do a top hat
一张脸 你也可以做一顶高帽
you could do a fedora you could do a
或者做一顶软呢帽
gown it's not a gown a tiara
抑或是一件长袍 噢 它不叫长袍 而是冕状头饰
that's what it's called thinking like Cinderella stuff
对 就是这么叫的 像灰姑娘一类的
and even one of those hats with
甚至是那些顶部有着
the cool little pinwheels on top.
凉爽降温的小风车的帽子
They're like the propellers you know
他们像螺旋桨那样运作 你懂的
It's a thing I don't know what's called the cool
这就像我并不知道什么能被称作凉爽的
after you do this you're going to create
但你做了这件事之后，你就在创造
the script. Oh the script is script
这个脚本 喔 就是这个脚本
is script is yes yes yes
没错这个脚本了
it's gonna look like this
它看起来就长这个样子
These are gonna be the general framework of it
它们就是基本的框架了
make sure you change the the text that it will say
确保改变它所说的文本
do something reasonable
做一些合理之事
once you have done so you will arrive at
一旦你这样做了你将会获得一些成果
something you're making fun of my artwork
你正在取笑我的插画
right now aren't you？You're
就刚刚 没有吗？你正在
making fun of that well guess what me
嘲笑它 好吧 你猜怎么着 我
and my mom both think it's amazing so
和我妈妈都认为它很神奇 所以它很
it's amazing. There it is. I'm a great
神奇。事实如此，我是一个伟大的
artist and there's that all right we
艺术家，而这就是我的作品。好吧我们
have our script we have our our model is
已经有了我们的脚本，我们的模型也已经
implemented here it's all this stuff
实现了所有的内容
right here we're ready we're ready to
我们已经 已经准备好
see if our magic has created a good hat
去看看我们的魔法是否已经创造了一顶优质的帽子
let's see how well our hat works
让我们来瞧瞧我们帽子有多棒
let us try some exact exact of Mundo quotes
我们现在试试孟多语录
from the Draco Malfoy himself
它来自德拉科·马尔福本人
yeah so one of the things that draco malfoy
德拉科·马尔福曾经
said was honestly if you were any
非常诚实地说过如果你
slower you'd be going backwards
慢一点，你就会倒退
what a charmer what a nice guy so this is a
他多么有魅力的好人啊。所以这就是一个
data point that we trained on
我们要训练过的数据点
This is the exact word edge that the model learned
这正是模型所学习到的措辞
so it doesn't give a Slytherin
所以它并不会带给斯莱特林
something is horribly awry
一些可怕的错误
and we may be doing pyromancy when we thought
并且我们可能认为自己在做火占卜
we were a frost mage so let's find out
我们是一个霜冻法师，所以让我们一起发现奥秘吧
I know about you but I was nervous what
我知道你不会 但是我很紧张
this means is that at the very minimum
从最简单的层面而言，这意味着
our hat has learned to memorize yes all
我们的帽子已经学会了记忆 太棒了
right let's look at some
现在让我们看看
other things that Ronald Weasley has
一些罗恩·韦斯莱曾经
spoken so one of the things he said is
don't let the muggles get you down for
anyone who doesn't know muggles are you
and me the people without magical powers
now we are gaining our magical powers
through the power of machine learning so
very soon we're gonna get our message in
the mail from the owls to hop on
Hogwarts and it will be awesome where we
learn to be full-fledged wizards
handedly amazing so here it worked it
actually worked
now we're going to try something a
little bit ambitious in fact so
ambitious that is the word that we're
going to use because chem vicious is
associated with the house of Slytherin
ambition at all costs so let's see if it
learned it it didn't it didn't learn it
what I want all this work I'm using the
magic of machine learning in here it
doesn't even learn that Slytherin is
ambitious
it's a bad hat yeah actually you're
right
you're not even ruffled you're correct
it's not a great hat okay
it's learned let's learn to memorize
okay it's learned a little bit about
Ronald Weasley it's learned a little bit
about Draco Malfoy look at that face but
it's not learned Slytherin
it is not learned Gryffindor and all
that that means if you watch those
movies if read those books but you like
get that so well so how did we get our
hat to be even better one of the things
you will hear more and more if you are
in the realm of data science at all
is more data you need more data you know
you need to see more of the you know
more about Harry Potter and more about
Hermione and all these famous Gryffindor
characters and then eventually you may
realize like okay I'm understanding the
essence of what it means to be a
Gryffindor or whatever so with our small
10 samples we've really learned because
what we trained on particularly was
quotes by Draco so we're gonna learn
Draco pretty well but he's not all of
Slytherin we've learned Ronald Weasley
pretty well but not necess
all of Gryffindor because I guess kind
of cheated if you want to say it like
that but that's what we have done and as
we see it works well for what we trained
on but if we look for things that we
have not trained on we probably need
more data to get a better vision of the
magical world all righty
we've made it ladies and gentlemen
welcome welcome to Hogwarts where we
learn with Sheena learning all day long
and become better wizards and more
friendly people all the day long we done
today what have we done well we created
a hat what does this hat do wonderful
question this hat is a classifier hat
all right so we have four classes right
we have our Gryffindor's we have our
slytherins and we have a hufflepuffs and
what we want to do is we want to tell is
this person just does he fit in here
does he is easy as leather is this ass
leather in person this is a is this a
ravenclaw see so Hufflepuff or perhaps a
Gryffindor now as we see it wasn't it
wasn't it wasn't easy okay it learns
some things but it didn't learn all
things and maybe your model when you
test it you know it does actually well
or it doesn't do very well on on certain
things and there many things we can do
to get that better but even the best
Wizards in the land I'm talking I'm
talking Godric Gryffindor I'm talking
I'm talking Harry Potter himself a
Dumbledore perhaps even dare I say it's
Voldemort that's right I said it
I did it they even have a hard time with
this okay these are very very difficult
spells to master natural language
processing is the type of magic that
this is this is not pyromancy we're not
being a frost mage or even a necromancer
okay this is known as natural language
processing because language it's natural
it's what we speak talking about wizards
and whatever and we want to you know
process this information we won't want
to know stuff about what we're saying
that's literally what that means is
knowing what the heck we're talking
about so it's really really hard and
even Dumbledore has a hard time so what
this means is that there's a ton of
research being done to this there are
great minds great Wizards doing
incredible things all over the globe to
attempt to get better at understanding
words so as we can see with our half
that we made here we can do some things
but it's still very hard so I hope we
have
sited some excitement towards the magic
of this great new realm known as natural
language processing also known as words
so once again this is Walker Stipe from
Palo Alto education hoping that you have
a wonderful wonderful day thank you and
goodbye